<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
	<name>AnyPlant</name>
	<author>alleZSoyez</author>
	<supportedVersions>
        <li>1.0</li>
        <li>1.1</li>
	<li>1.2</li>
	<li>1.3</li>
	<li>1.4</li>
        <li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>alleZSoyez.AnyPlant.AnyPlant</packageId>
	<description>AnyPlant: Because two is never enough.
This is my first mod ever. Please let me know if you find any issues.
Special thanks to the fine folks at Ludeon Forums for helping me with some retexturing and for helping me fix that glowstool bug...
Special thanks also to Karmapowered for pointing out an incompatibility with the healroot. Please let me know if the issues with that plant perist.

FEATURES:
- Grow nearly any plant that exists in vanilla Rimworld in a pot!
- Custom plants! Cultivate beautiful hydrangeas in three different colors!
- Decorate your colony with bonsai trees!
- Fixed the problem in vanilla where potted roses grow outside the pot! (This fix also affects the vanilla plant pots.)
- Plant crops inside all year round! They'll grow faster and with less light and are easier to protect from the elements. For balance, harvestable plants only produce half as many resources.
- Even grow your own ambrosia!

In the interest of keeping the game balanced (especially early-game), research is required to unlock the pot as well as the various plants. Ambrosia is intended for long-term research. If you have any recommendations to better balance this mod, I'd love to hear them!

This mod is not intended to replace the normal ways of growing crops outside/in hydroponic basins and should not be relied upon to feed a hungry colony. This is more of a novelty item and is better suited for mid-to-late game.

WARNINGS:
- I do not recommend adding this to a game in progress. Unexpected things might happen. If they do, please let me know about them.
- I also do not recommend removing this mod from a save file. If you want to try anyway, make sure you've deleted every plant pot on the map first (this mod also affects vanilla pots in order to fix the roses).
		</description>
</ModMetaData>
